Frank O. and Daisy Beck papers, 1890-1969 C168
Indiana University Archives
- Correspondence, 1899-1967; undated (Box 8)
  - Keating, Winifred, 1934 (Box 9)
  - Kellogg, Hiram W., ca. 1904 (Box 9)
  - Kepler, Helen, 1949-1962 (Box 9)
  - Kralis, Lieut. Frank, ca. 1944 (Box 9)
  - General L, 1906-1962; undated (Box 9)
  - Lasbury, Mrs. Edwin, 1959-1961 (Box 9)
  - Laury, Raymond H., 1940-1942 (Box 9)
  - Ledheller, Marth, 1942-1946 (Box 9)
  - Leslie, Albert C., 1944 (Box 9)
  - Leslie, Ronald, 1910-1917 (Box 9)
  - Lindquist, Margaret, 1946-1947 (Box 9)
  - Littell, Guy, 1951; undated (Box 9)
  - Losche, Corp. Albert, 1943-1950 (Box 9)
  - General M, 1909-1965 (Box 9)
  - Marston, Al, 1950-1958; undated (Box 9)
  - Martin, Charlotte, 1936-1946 (Box 9)
  - Maurer, Ethel, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Maurer, Mrs. William F., 1945-1946 (Box 9)
  - McAlister, A.W., ca. 1912 (Box 9)
  - McConnel, T.J., 1910 (Box 9)
  - McDowell, William F., 1912 (Box 9)
  - McKown, E.M., 1940 (Box 9)
  - Meacham, Paul L., 1939-1942 (Box 9)
  - Methodist Book Concern, 1912-1940 (Box 9)
  - Methodist Federation for Social Service, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
  - Meyer, Lt. Max, 1940-1943 (Box 9)
  - Midwest Council on Speakers on International Relations, 1937-1938 (Box 9)
  - Mid-West Institute of International Relations, 1935-1936 (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2 folders, 1910-1966; undated (Box 9)
  - Moeckel, Marie, 1934-1936 (Box 9)
  - Moore, Aubrey, 1941-1946 (Box 9)
  - Moore, Jeanne Ann, 1943-1945 (Box 9)
  - Moore, John Edward, 1943-1947 (Box 9)
  - Moores Hill College – Related Correspondence, 1904-1907 (Box 9)
  - Moran, Betty and Dick, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Mount, Huston, ca. 1943 (Box 9)
  - General N-P, 1912-1965; undated (Box 9)
  - National Christian Mission, 1940 (Box 9)
  - National College of Education, 1934 (Box 9)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1940-1947 (Box 9)
  - Nesmith, Anna C., 1925-1964 (Box 9)
  - Nicholson, Thomas, 1911-1914 (Box 9)
  - Norris, 2nd Lt. Charles R., ca. 1942 (Box 9)
  - Northcraft, Clifford, 1950 (Box 9)
  - Olofson, Andy and Betty, 1940-1944 (Box 9)
  - Palmer, Charles, 1936-1937 (Box 9)
  - Patrick, J.E., 1944-1965 (Box 9)
  - Phillips, George, 1934-1947 (Box 9)
  - Pierce, Robert B., 1952-1963 (Box 9)
  - General R, 1915-1967 (Box 9)
  - Ragatz, B.J., 1960-1963 (Box 9)
  - Rand, Sally, 1931-1932 (Box 9)
  - Rawlings, Lola D., 1962 (Box 9)
  - Reconciliation Trips, 1934-1941 (Box 9)
  - Rees, Mary, 1941 (Box 9)
  - Refugee Related, 1939-1941 (Box 9)
  - Reid, Richard, 1952-1958 (Box 9)
  - Reitman, Rose, 1933-1936 (Box 9)
  - Rock River Annual Conference, Board of Conference Claimants, 1937-1944 (Box 10)
  - Rosenthal, Alice, 1941 (Box 10)
  - General S, 1912-1965; undated (Box 10)
  - Schricker, Henry F., 1938-1940 (Box 10)
  - Scott, Roland, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Sears, Louis, 1935 (Box 10)
  - Shafer, Alvia Beck, 1899-1952; undated (Box 10)
  - Sheridan, Thomas E., 1947-1966 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Epsilon Theta, 1939 (Box 10)
  - Sigma Nu Fraternity, 1938-1965; undated (Box 10)
  - Smith, Pvt. Dwight L., 1943-1945 (Box 10)
  - Smith, Robert Morris, 1949-1952 (Box 10)
  - State Young Men's Christian Association, 1945-1946 (Box 10)
  - Stein, Rose, 1956-1959 (Box 10)
  - Stephenson, Robert and Elizabeth, 1936-1947 (Box 10)
  - Strain, Julia, 1942-1948 (Box 10)
  - Student Government, 1963 (Box 10)
  - Student in Military Service – Addresses, undated (Box 10)
  - Sturgeon, Robert, 1937-1943 (Box 10)
  - General T-V, 1935-1966; undated (Box 10)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1938-1939 (Box 10)
  - Tiemeyer, Delores, 1949-1950 (Box 10)
  - Trippet, Sanford, 1955-1962; undated (Box 10)
  - Ulmet, A. A., 1960; undated (Box 10)
  - Vincent, John H., 1897-1904 (Box 10)
  - Visher, PFC John, 1943-1952 (Box 10)
  - Volpert, Pvt. James F., 1943 (Box 10)
  - General W-Z, 1912-1965; undated (Box 10)
  - Walker, John, 1917-1948 (Box 11)
  - Waltz, Ralph, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
  - Wasoske, Mary, 1941 (Box 11)
  - Wayfarers Lodger No. 1001, 1941 (Box 11)
  - Wedding Invitations – Miscellaneous, 1941-1943; undated (Box 11)
  - Wells, Herman B, 1935-1955 (Box 11)
  - Wilkinson, Dolores Grice, 1939-1945 (Box 11)
  - Wilson, Ray C., 1944-1945 (Box 11)
  - Wright, Grace, 1939 (Box 11)
  - Young American Wants to Help, 1941 (Box 11)
  - Young, Jack, 1950-1961; undated (Box 11)
  - Young Men's Christian Association, 1941-1946 (Box 11)
  - Zuppman, Edith Evans, 1941-1944 (Box 11)
- RESTRICTED FILES (Box 11)